<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/feeds/rss/videos/rssfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><title>News Videos Online: HD Videos Online, Video News Clips, Funny HD Videos Online | Hindustan Times</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos</link><description><![CDATA[<p>News Videos Online – Browse and Watch High Definition News Videos, Funny Videos, Technology Videos, Reviews, Bollywood Interviews, Celebrities Gossip, Controversy, Live Rally Videos and many more at hindustantimes.com.</p>]]></description><category>videos</category><ttl>60</ttl><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 16:58:49 +0530</lastBuildDate><copyright>Copyright (C) 2019 HT Media Limited. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><language>en-US</language><docs>https://www.hindustantimes.com</docs><image><title>News Videos Online: HD Videos Online, Video News Clips, Funny HD Videos Online | Hindustan Times</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos</link><url>https://www.hindustantimes.com/images/app-images/ht2020/desktop.png</url></image><item><title><![CDATA[Hanuman controversy at Aero India 2023 | HAL removes pic from HLFT-42 aircraft]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Hindustan Aeronautics Limited removed a picture of Lord Hanuman from one of their aircraft at the Aero India 2023 following a controversy. HAL had showcased the full-scale model of its supersonic trainer aircraft HLFT-42 with a picture of Lord Hanuman on its tail. HAL earlier said they had decided to use Hanuman's picture to display the power of the aircraft, however the decision to remove it came after an internal discussion. Aero India 2023 is Asia's largest aero show and it was inaugurated by Prime Minister Narendra Modi. The 5-day event will see participation of 809 companies and delegates from 98 countries. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/hanuman-controversy-at-aero-india-2023-hal-removes-pic-from-tail-of-hlft-42-aircraft-101676373286180.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/hanuman-controversy-at-aero-india-2023-hal-removes-pic-from-tail-of-hlft-42-aircraft-101676373286180.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 16:47:27 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/THUMBHAL_1676373375648_1676373380315_1676373380315.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[India salutes Pulwama braves | '8 of 19 terrorists involved in attack killed']]></title><description><![CDATA[On the fourth anniversary of the dastardly terror attack in Pulwama that claimed the lives of over 40 soldiers, India is remembering the valour of its heroes and their supreme sacrifice. Tributes poured in from PM Narendra Modi, Home Minister Amit Shah and Congress leader Rahul Gandhi. The Army, CRPF, J&K police laid floral wreaths on the memorial for the martyrs in Pulwama. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/as-india-salutes-pulwama-bravehearts-8-of-19-terrorists-involved-in-attack-killed-i-details-101676370345789.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/as-india-salutes-pulwama-bravehearts-8-of-19-terrorists-involved-in-attack-killed-i-details-101676370345789.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:57:31 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail__1676370423786_1676370430339_1676370430339.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amit Shah rejects 'erasing Mughal history' charge amid BJP's 'Lucknow as Laxmanpur' demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amit Shah, the Home Minister, responds sharply to allegations of erasing Mughal history. Responding to a question on the Mughal legacy, Shah said that the BJP does not want to remove anybody's contribution to history, including that of the Mughals. The Home Minister also defended the renaming spree in BJP-ruled states and said not a single city that previously did not have an old name has been changed. The statement comes just days after U.P. Deputy CM Brajesh Pathak appealed to change the name of Lucknow as it is "well known as the city of Laxman." After this, BJP MP Sangam Lal Gupta urged Union Home Minister Amit Shah to rename U.P.'s capital city of Lucknow as "Lakhanpur" or "Laxmanpur."]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/amit-shah-rejects-erasing-mughal-history-charge-amid-bjp-s-lucknow-as-laxmanpur-demand-101676370201242.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/amit-shah-rejects-erasing-mughal-history-charge-amid-bjp-s-lucknow-as-laxmanpur-demand-101676370201242.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:56:33 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILI_1676370296255_1676370313244_1676370313244.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S ‘spy’ balloon saga a ploy? Sensational claim amid row over Nord Stream ‘sabotage’ | Details]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back-to-back UFO "dramas" have raised several questions over the claims made by the United States. Former U.S. NSA (National Security Agency) employee and whistleblower Edward Snowden says shot-down UFOs are meant to divert attention from Nord Stream sabotage. "The security panic is also engineered for political misdirection," claims Snowden. Seymour Hersh, an American journalist, published an article on February 8 detailing how the United States and Norway blew up Nord Stream pipelines transporting Russian natural gas to Germany in September. The investigative report on Nord Stream sabotage was denounced as false by the U.S. government. After this, over the next several days, the U.S. military began shooting down "objects" in the skies. While the first so-called "spy balloon" belonged to China, the U.S., which is now under fire, says it is not sure if the other three flying objects it downed were spying. Watch this report for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/us-spy-balloon-saga-a-ploy-sensational-claim-amid-row-over-nord-stream-sabotage-details-101676365061989.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/us-spy-balloon-saga-a-ploy-sensational-claim-amid-row-over-nord-stream-sabotage-details-101676365061989.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:30:18 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILspy_1676365163196_1676365184159_1676365184159.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lanka rejects LTTE Chief alive claim; 'Prabhakaran was killed. DNA proved it']]></title><description><![CDATA[Sri Lanka has dismissed as joke the claims that LTTE Chief Prabhakaran was alive. Pazha Nedumaran, a noted nationalist leader in Tamil Nadu, said on February 13 that the leader of the LTTE 'is doing well and a conducive atmosphere prevails for him to appear now.' "It is confirmed that he was killed on 19 May 2009. The DNA has proved it," said Colonel Nalin Herath, Sri Lanka's defence ministry spokesperson. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/joke-lanka-rejects-ltte-chief-alive-claim-prabhakaran-was-killed-dna-proved-it-101676364628352.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/joke-lanka-rejects-ltte-chief-alive-claim-prabhakaran-was-killed-dna-proved-it-101676364628352.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:22:59 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail_-_1676364750318_1676364756339_1676364756339.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Treasure’: Sarojini Naidu’s 1928 speech in US gives Indians goosebumps | Viral]]></title><description><![CDATA[A 95-year-old video of Sarojini Naidu has now gone viral on social media. The video from her 1928 visit to the United States is giving goosebumps to netizens on her birth anniversary. The 55-second clip was shared by former Minister of Climate and the Environment of Norway, Erik Solheim, on Twitter. In the video, Naidu delivers a motivational speech about how, as a woman, she represents India in the 'new world.' The video has garnered over 1,81,000 views since it was shared. Watch the full video here. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/treasure-sarojini-naidu-s-1928-speech-in-u-s-gives-indians-goosebumps-in-2023-viral-101676359112045.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/treasure-sarojini-naidu-s-1928-speech-in-u-s-gives-indians-goosebumps-in-2023-viral-101676359112045.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:50:11 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/THUMB_NAIDU_1676359181904_1676359186635_1676359186635.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pak Goes Bankrupt: Chicken costs PKR 900, milk PKR 210 as inflation ‘crosses all limits’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pakistan's dire economic state has hit its citizens hard with skyrocketing prices. Prices of daily-use items across Pakistan are on fire after the International Monetary Fund (IMF) sought more time to conclude a $1.1 billion loan tranche. People are struggling to put necessary food items on the table, such as milk and chicken, which are common principal items in Pakistani meals. The country's inflation is at a 48-year high, and foreign currency reserves cover less than a month of imports. Pakistanis say inflation has "crossed all limits," lamenting the IMF conditions. Prime Minister Shehbaz Sharif has said that the Pakistani government would have to agree to IMF bailout conditions that are "beyond imagination." Watch this report for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/pak-goes-bankrupt-chicken-costs-pkr-900-milk-pkr-210-as-inflation-crosses-all-limits-101676358324351.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/pak-goes-bankrupt-chicken-costs-pkr-900-milk-pkr-210-as-inflation-crosses-all-limits-101676358324351.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:37:51 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailPAKSS_1676358437182_1676358454322_1676358454322.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia bombs Donetsk frontline with all might | How Ukrainian Resistance Broke]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russia has claimed that in the past 4 days its forces managed to shift the frontline 2 kms to the West amid bloody Ukraine war. Russian defence ministry has now released footage showing how Russian soldiers achieved the feat. Dramatic videos show how Russian soldiers detected Ukrainian strongholds along the frontline and bombed them in a bid to break the Ukrainian resistance. Watch this video to find out more about what is happening along the 1,500 km-long frontline as war anniversary nears. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/russian-army-bombs-donetsk-frontline-with-all-might-watch-how-ukrainian-resistance-broke-101676357658554.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/russian-army-bombs-donetsk-frontline-with-all-might-watch-how-ukrainian-resistance-broke-101676357658554.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:25:51 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/THUMB_WAR_VIDEO_1676357719636_1676357724852_1676357724852.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin's new target days before invasion anniversary alarms NATO; Bakhmut's fall imminent | Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[Days before the one-year anniversary of Russia's invasion of Ukraine, Vladimir Putin's army has launched an all-new onslaught across the line of contact. The eastern Ukrainian city of Bakhmut is the centre of new bombardments. According to The New York Times, Kyiv has barred civilians from entering Bakhmut, which could be a precursor to a Ukrainian withdrawal from the city. Before February 24, the first anniversary of the invasion, Russia seems to have set a deadline to "liberate" the region that Putin annexed last October. Russia's ferocious launch of a new offensive has also alarmed NATO. Watch this video for full information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putins-new-target-days-before-invasion-anniversary-alarms-nato-bakhmut-s-fall-imminent-watch-101676351254058.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putins-new-target-days-before-invasion-anniversary-alarms-nato-bakhmut-s-fall-imminent-watch-101676351254058.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 10:40:04 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnailputoff_1676351302903_1676351319958_1676351319958.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. training Islamic terrorists to strike  Moscow | Russian Intel Amid Ukraine War]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russia’s foreign intelligence service (SVR) has made a bombshell accusation against the U.S. The SVR claimed that U.S military is planning to conduct terror attacks in Russia & Ex-Soviet states. As per the Russian agency SVR, U.S is actively recruiting jihadists affiliated to Al-Qaeda & Islamic State and is training them at a U.S base in Syria to attack Russia. Watch this report for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/us-training-islamic-terrorists-to-strike-moscow-russian-intel-amid-ukraine-war-101676345144650.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/us-training-islamic-terrorists-to-strike-moscow-russian-intel-amid-ukraine-war-101676345144650.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 08:57:53 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnailsvr_1676345231560_1676345253495_1676345253495.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin’s war drains UK arsenal? British Army flags ‘serious weapons shortage’ as Sunak arms Kyiv]]></title><description><![CDATA[The British military is reportedly stretched as Rishi Sunak mulls sending fighter jets to Ukraine. The Daily Mail reported that the British Army is having serious problems with ammunition shortages because of the amount of ammo and other ordnance being supplied to Ukraine. An unnamed source at the UK's Ministry of Defence told the newspaper that British forces are also stretched because of the extent to which they are training Ukrainian forces. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/putins-war-drains-uk-arsenal-british-army-flags-serious-weapons-shortage-as-sunak-arms-kyiv-101676338345976.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/putins-war-drains-uk-arsenal-british-army-flags-serious-weapons-shortage-as-sunak-arms-kyiv-101676338345976.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 07:05:47 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailSIII_1676338431237_1676338450699_1676338450699.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[“I always know if my films will work or not” - Yami Gautam | Lost]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yami Gautam is all set for her upcoming release 'Lost' helmed by Aniruddha Roy Chowdhury. Yami Gautam opens up about her journey in this episode of Aur Batao. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/entertainment/i-always-know-if-my-films-will-work-or-not-yami-gautam-lost-101676310511769.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/entertainment/i-always-know-if-my-films-will-work-or-not-yami-gautam-lost-101676310511769.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:19:40 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676310508991_1676310508991_1676310539160_1676310539160.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Thank PM Modi for...'; Sonam Wangchuk on saving Ladakh - Interview]]></title><description><![CDATA[The story of Sonam Wangchuk's 'climate fast' at minus 40° celsius. Environmentalist & innovator Sonam Wangchuk fasts to 'save Ladakh'. In the interview to Hindustan Times, Wangchuk said that despite the fast, sixth schedule of constitution remains a sticking point. Watch this interaction to know more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/thank-pm-modi-for-sonam-wangchuk-on-saving-ladakh-interview-101676310301985.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/thank-pm-modi-for-sonam-wangchuk-on-saving-ladakh-interview-101676310301985.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:16:13 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676310298691_1676310298691_1676310322663_1676310322663.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[NATO stockpiles in dire straits as Ukraine army needs outstrips production rate]]></title><description><![CDATA[NATO has said it will increase targets for stockpiling ammunition as Kyiv is burning through shells much faster than Western countries can produce them and after a year of conflict in Ukraine has left allied stocks badly depleted. The West needed to ramp up production, with the waiting time for large-calibre ammunition increasing to 28 months from 12 months, Stoltenberg said. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/nato-stockpiles-in-dire-straits-as-ukraine-military-needs-outstrips-production-rate-i-details-101676307622393.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/nato-stockpiles-in-dire-straits-as-ukraine-military-needs-outstrips-production-rate-i-details-101676307622393.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 22:31:52 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676307618441_1676307618441_1676307644319_1676307644319.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tamil Leader’s shocking claim about LTTE Chief Prabhakaran | ‘Alive &…' I Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[A veteran former politician in Tamil Nadu Pazha Nedumaran has made a shocking claim. He says LTTE Chief Prabhakaran, who was declared dead by the Sri Lankan govt 14 years ago, is alive and healthy. Nedumaran says Prabhakaran will soon make a public appearance. Prabhakaran, the founder of Liberation of Tigers of Tamil Eelam (LTTE), led an extensive guerrilla campaign for a separate homeland for Lankan Tamils in the island nation. He was declared dead on May 18, 2009 after an operation by the Sri Lankan army at Mullivaikal. Addressing a briefing, Pazha Nedumaran, the President of the Worlds Tamil Confederation, said 'LTTE chief Prabhakaran is alive and will appear soon. We are happy to announce this to the world. He would announce his plans for Tamil Eelam'. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/tamil-leader-s-shocking-claim-about-ltte-chief-prabhakaran-alive-will-appear-in-public-101676303334334.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/tamil-leader-s-shocking-claim-about-ltte-chief-prabhakaran-alive-will-appear-in-public-101676303334334.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:20:46 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676303331906_1676303331906_1676303364014_1676303364014.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Can they land?': Taliban's Air Force pilots roasted on social media I Here's Why]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taliban's Air force reportedly got three new pilots. A photograph of three men holding ‘pilot licence’ with a picture of helicopter embossed on certificate has gone viral on social media. The three bare-footed men wearing traditional Afghani attire can be seen holding certificates in their hands while sitting in an office. Watch this video for more]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/can-they-land-taliban-s-air-force-pilots-roasted-on-social-media-i-here-s-why-101676301227863.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/can-they-land-taliban-s-air-force-pilots-roasted-on-social-media-i-here-s-why-101676301227863.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:44:55 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676301224969_1676301224969_1676301259890_1676301259890.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[NATO nation warns EU against escalating Putin’s war by sending arms to Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hungary has yet again warned the European union against arming Ukraine. The foreign minister of the NATO nation claimed that continued weapons supply to Ukraine will only escalate the conflict with Russia. Speaking to radio Kossuth, Peter Szijjarto slammed the decisions of EU lawmakers on Ukraine and said that they have generally caused damage to Europe and further weapons deliveries will only worsen the hostilities. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/nato-nation-warns-eu-against-escalating-putin-s-war-by-sending-more-arms-to-ukraine-101676300541686.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/nato-nation-warns-eu-against-escalating-putin-s-war-by-sending-more-arms-to-ukraine-101676300541686.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:34:15 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/THUMBNAILEUROPE_WARNS_1676300608356_1676300629755_1676300629755.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel’s Jerusalem ‘Revenge’; Netanyahu legalises nine more West Bank settlements]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a first such move by the Netanyahu cabinet, the Israeli government has authourised nine Jewish settlements in the West Bank which were previously unauthourised outposts. Israeli PM Netanyahu's office has called a decision a response to recent attacks in East Jerusalem. The move has drawn condemnation from the Palestinian Authority which called it an 'open war' against its people. Netanyahu's office said more housing units are likely to be built in separate, existing illegal settlements. The decision comes amid escalating Israeli-Palestinian violence, with at least 46 Palestinians killed so far this year. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/israels-jerusalem-revenge-netanyahu-legalises-nine-more-west-bank-settlements-101676297572089.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/israels-jerusalem-revenge-netanyahu-legalises-nine-more-west-bank-settlements-101676297572089.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:48:42 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/thumbisr_1676297848575_1676297851623_1676297851623.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[China ‘exposes’ U.S., ‘spots' over 10 American ‘Spy’ balloons in airspace]]></title><description><![CDATA[China has now accused the U.S. of sending over 10 'spy' balloons in its airspace since 2022. The tensions between the two nations are at an all time high, after the U.S. shot down Chinese 'airship' earlier this month. China also added that the 'spy' balloon is not an uncommon phenomenon and that the U.S. should respond to its act. This comes at a time when U.S. shot down a fourth object in the North American airspace in the last 7 days and also at a time when China is preparing to shoot down an UFO over the Yellow Sea near Qingdao Port in Shandong province. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/china-exposes-u-s-claims-spotting-over-10-american-spy-balloons-in-airspace-details-101676296869057.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/china-exposes-u-s-claims-spotting-over-10-american-spy-balloons-in-airspace-details-101676296869057.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:34:45 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail_1676296953010_1676297068175_1676297068175.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin's 'Nazi' claims genuine? Zelensky shares soldier’s pic with skull insignia]]></title><description><![CDATA[An image shared by Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky seems to prove Russian leader Vladimir Putin's Nazi claims about Kyiv's forces right. Ukrainian President Zelensky has posted a photo of a soldier sporting a symbol used by a notorious German unit that killed civilians in World War II. It is not the first time Ukrainian soldiers and paramilitaries have been photographed displaying insignia and tattoos associated with Nazism. The black-and-white skull-head patch on the soldier’s arm in the pic shared by Zelensky is similar to the "Totenkopf" insignia used by Adolf Hitler’s elite SS units. Notably, Ukraine's Azov Regiment, which is currently fighting Russians, is also well known for welcoming fighters with openly Nazi views. Remember, Russian President Vladimir Putin claims that "denazification" is one of the reasons Moscow launched a military operation in Ukraine. Watch this report for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/putins-nazi-claims-genuine-russia-fumes-as-zelensky-shares-soldier-s-pic-with-skull-insignia-101676295141864.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/putins-nazi-claims-genuine-russia-fumes-as-zelensky-shares-soldier-s-pic-with-skull-insignia-101676295141864.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:04:55 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/thumbpu_1676295203263_1676295206343_1676295206343.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Can't break Russia': Putin's ally lambasts West; Rebukes partition plot]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin's ally and Chechen Leader, Ramzan Kadyrov, rebukes Ukraine's stunning claims of "change on the Russian border soon." The Chechen leader said that "Russia's map can be redrawn only when Moscow decides." Ramzan Kadyrov said that such attempts to break Russia have been made by the West since the 1990s, but these overconfident people will fail. The Chechen warlord's remarks came after Alexey Danielov, Secretary of Ukraine's National Security and Defence Council, made claims about Russia's partition. Alexey Danielov said that "Russia is a colonial state that will soon split up." Watch this report for full information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/cant-break-russia-putin-s-ally-lambasts-west-chechan-warlord-rebukes-partition-plot-details-101676293377954.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/cant-break-russia-putin-s-ally-lambasts-west-chechan-warlord-rebukes-partition-plot-details-101676293377954.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:34:08 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676293375372_1676293375372_1676293396109_1676293396109.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel jets drop missiles on Hamas rocket factory in Gaza, destroys 'underground sites' I Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israel launched overnight air strikes against a Hamas complex in Gaza in response to a rocket fired from the Palestinian enclave, the military said early Monday. Following the Israeli strikes, air raid sirens sounded in communities in near the Gaza border, the military said, but there was no immediate confirmation of retaliatory Palestinian rocket fire on Monday. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/israel-jets-drop-missiles-on-hamas-rocket-factory-in-gaza-destroys-underground-sites-i-watch-101676292348154.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/israel-jets-drop-missiles-on-hamas-rocket-factory-in-gaza-destroys-underground-sites-i-watch-101676292348154.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:17:03 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676292344363_1676292344363_1676292371063_1676292371063.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[India 'receives' Russian arms worth $13 BN; Modi-Putin defence brotherhood stuns West | Details]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russia has "supplied India with around $13 billion of arms" during the past 5 years. According to Russian state news agencies, New Delhi has placed orders with Moscow for weapons and military equipment worth more than $10 billion. Notably, India is the world's biggest buyer of Russian arms, accounting for around 20% of Moscow's current weapons order book. Remember, New Delhi has not explicitly condemned Russia's invasion of Ukraine. India's Prime Minister Narendra Modi has called for dialogue and diplomacy to solve the Ukraine conflict but has refused to cut off ties with Moscow. Most western countries have imposed sanctions on Russia, including on its arms. Russia has praised India for not backing down in the face of western pressure. Watch this report for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/india-receives-russian-arms-worth-13-bn-modi-putin-defence-brotherhood-stuns-west-details-101676289030828.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/india-receives-russian-arms-worth-13-bn-modi-putin-defence-brotherhood-stuns-west-details-101676289030828.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:22:53 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILIND_RUSSIA_1676289069954_1676289089329_1676289089329.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch dramatic Russian video of tanks raining ‘hell-fire’ on Ukrainian soldiers]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Russian Defence Ministry has released dramatic footage of an armoured group of airborne combat vehicles BMD-2K-AU, BMPT Terminator and BTR-D with an anti-aircraft artillery installation ZU-23 opening non-stop fire at Ukrainian stronghold. The drones first detected the platoon of Ukrainian soldiers and then launched an all-out attack. In another video, a Howitzer crew can be seen pounding Ukrainian positions with artillery. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/dramatic-russian-footage-of-tanks-raining-hell-fire-on-trapped-ukrainian-soldiers-watch-101676287282795.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/dramatic-russian-footage-of-tanks-raining-hell-fire-on-trapped-ukrainian-soldiers-watch-101676287282795.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:53:22 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail_1676287377020_1676287383027_1676287383027.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch IAF war machine Prachand’s aerobatic display at Aero India 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aero India 2023 witnessed thrilling aerobatics by made-in-India Light Combat Helicopter 'Prachand' which left the audience mesmerised. LCH 'Prachand' is the world's only attack helicopter suitable for flying at high altitudes. It has been designed and developed by Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd and was formally commissioned into the Indian Air Force in 2022. The multi-role attack helicopter can damage enemy's air defence activities and fire a variety of air-to-ground and air-to-air missiles.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-iaf-war-machine-prachand-s-captivating-aerobatic-display-at-aero-india-2023-101676284455983.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-iaf-war-machine-prachand-s-captivating-aerobatic-display-at-aero-india-2023-101676284455983.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:06:32 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/prachnd_1676284519623_1676284524072_1676284524072.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Putin Can Win The War': NATO nation's big admission; Poland pushes for more arms to Ukraine]]></title><description><![CDATA[The NATO nation's leader makes a sensational statement on Russia's possible victory. Russia may win the Ukraine conflict if the Kyiv government does not receive more Western weapons in the coming weeks, according to Polish President Andrzej Duda. The Polish President clearly admitted during an interview that "Yes, Russia can win." The NATO leader's comments didn’t go unnoticed by the Russian government. Responding to the statement, the Russian Foreign Ministry said that even if western weapons are supplied to Kyiv quickly, they "won’t be able to change the outcome of the war." Watch this report for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putin-can-win-the-war-nato-nation-s-big-admission-poland-pushes-for-more-arms-to-ukraine-101676282066434.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putin-can-win-the-war-nato-nation-s-big-admission-poland-pushes-for-more-arms-to-ukraine-101676282066434.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:26:29 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailWIN_1676282084084_1676282107239_1676282107239.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Julie went & barked’: How India’s dog duo saved girl from Turkey quake rubble]]></title><description><![CDATA[On February 9, two Indian dogs were instrumental in saving the life of a 6-year-old girl, who was trapped inside the rubble in earthquake-ravaged Turkey. Four days after the miracle, dog handler Constable Kundan explains how Labrador Julie found the little girl, Beren, alive first in the rubble at the Nurdagi site. He added that Romeo and Julie succeeded where machines failed and said that without their help, the little girl could not have survived. Under 'Operation Dost,' India has sent a four-member dog squad to Turkey to help NDRF's search and rescue. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/julie-went-in-and-barked-how-india-s-dog-duo-rescued-girl-from-rubble-in-quake-hit-turkey-101676280947070.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/julie-went-in-and-barked-how-india-s-dog-duo-rescued-girl-from-rubble-in-quake-hit-turkey-101676280947070.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:09:19 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/THUMB_INDIAN_DOGS_1676281125747_1676281130395_1676281130395.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia breaks Ukrainian resistance; Putin’s men advance 2 KM West of frontline]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russian Army has succeeded in breaking the resistance of the Ukrainian soldiers at the frontline. News agency Interfax quoted Russian defence ministry to claim that the Army had advanced 2 km deeper and moved the frontline to the west. It however did not specify in which region the frontline had moved. A fierce fighting in underway in the Donetsk region as Russian Army aims to capture the entire eastern region in Ukraine. The Russian defence ministry also claimed that the troops had eliminated over 240 Ukrainian troops in the past day. It added that Ukraine was shelling Donetsk cities thrice in an hour and carried out over 40 attacks in the last 24 hours. Watch this video for more updates from the battleground.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/russian-army-breaks-ukrainian-resistance-putin-s-men-advance-2-km-shift-frontline-to-west-101676280775413.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/russian-army-breaks-ukrainian-resistance-putin-s-men-advance-2-km-shift-frontline-to-west-101676280775413.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:05:36 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailWin_1676280896910_1676280901463_1676280901463.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Tejas jets dazzle at Aero India 2023 | PM Modi lauds ‘Aatmanirbhar Bharat’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi inaugurated Asia's largest aero show, Aero India 2023, in Bengaluru. The 14th edition of the aero show will display made-in-India equipment and technologies to forge partnership with foreign companies. Addressing the inauguration ceremony, PM Modi said that Aero India reflects the country's new strengths and aspirations. The five-day event, on the theme 'The runway to a billion opportunities' will showcase India's growth in aerospace and defence capabilities. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-tejas-jets-dazzle-at-aero-india-2023-pm-modi-lauds-aatmanirbhar-bharat-101676278111145.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-tejas-jets-dazzle-at-aero-india-2023-pm-modi-lauds-aatmanirbhar-bharat-101676278111145.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:20:33 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/thummotejas_1676278205480_1676278208475_1676278208475.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Op Dost: Army-made fixators help Turkey quake survivors | Display At Aero India]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indian Army has become a beacon of hope for several earthquake survivors in Turkey and Syria. The Indian Army has set up a field hospital in Turkey's Hatay, where doctors have deployed light fixators that help treat fractures. These fixators weigh only five grams and cost  ₹300 each. They are developed by the Indian Army and have been used by over 200 patients till now. Colonel Vijay Adarsh, the developer of this fixator displayed his product at the Aero India 2023 event in Bengaluru today. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/op-dost-army-made-fixators-help-turkey-syria-quake-survivors-on-display-at-aero-india-101676276873566.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/op-dost-army-made-fixators-help-turkey-syria-quake-survivors-on-display-at-aero-india-101676276873566.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:03:36 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumb_1676277329181_1676277334711_1676277334711.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan Match Highlights | Women's T20 World Cup | Cricket Canvas]]></title><description><![CDATA[India beat Pakistan and kickstarted their T20 WC campaign. Blue and Green clashed once again at one of the biggest platforms of cricket. Although India had the upper hand through the years, with four victories in 6 confrontations, Pakistan gave India a run for their money. But the Women-in-Blue came out on top. Here are the match highlights and match review of the India-Pakistan Women’s T20WC match. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/cricket/india-vs-pakistan-match-highlights-women-s-t20-world-cup-cricket-canvas-101676271255391.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/cricket/india-vs-pakistan-match-highlights-women-s-t20-world-cup-cricket-canvas-101676271255391.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 12:26:20 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676271252539_1676271252539_1676271272035_1676271272035.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Pak, Dhokla & 2 AM Call': Ex-Army Officer on Shah’s final Srinagar visit before 370 move]]></title><description><![CDATA[Union Home Minister Amit Shah's visit to Srinagar in June 2019 was intended to "put the finishing touches" on the government's determination to repeal Article 370. Inside details of Amit Shah's 370 Purge Plan have been revealed by Lt. Gen. (R) KJS Dhillon in his yet-to-be-released book, "Kitne Ghazi Aaye, Kitne Ghazi Gaye." Lt. Gen. (R) KJS Dhillon said that a lot of sensitive issues and key points were on the table for discussion, apart from the delectable food that included aloo paratha and the famous Gujarati dish dhokla. Dhillon also revealed that Amit Shah had asked for his personal view on the government's decision, to which he had replied, "Agar itihaas likhna hai, toh kisi ko itihas banana padega" (we can write history only if we make history). Lt. General (R) Dhillon was heading the local army command in Kashmir when the landmark decision was taken by the Modi government in 2019. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/pak-dhokla-2-am-call-ex-army-officer-on-shah-s-final-srinagar-visit-before-370-move-101676268976124.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/pak-dhokla-2-am-call-ex-army-officer-on-shah-s-final-srinagar-visit-before-370-move-101676268976124.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:48:42 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILARI_1676269078607_1676269094565_1676269094565.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Strike London': Putin's ally calls for attack on UK after Sunak's fresh arms aid to Ukraine | Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[A staunch ally of Russian President Vladimir Putin, Vladimir Solovyov, has called for striking the UK parliament while criticising the West for supporting Ukraine. "What's the problem with striking London?" asked Solovyov, who is a Russian state TV host. He called the UK, France, and Germany Nazi states united by hatred for everything Russian. The statement was made during a show on Moscow's state television, "Russia 1." Remember, Moscow has repeatedly accused London of provoking Kyiv with arms aid. The stunning remarks come days after Russia threatened a "bloody harvest" in war if the United Kingdom sent fighter jets to Ukraine's battlefield. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/worldview/strike-london-putin-s-ally-calls-for-attack-on-uk-after-sunak-s-fresh-arms-aid-to-ukraine-watch-101676265386485.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/worldview/strike-london-putin-s-ally-calls-for-attack-on-uk-after-sunak-s-fresh-arms-aid-to-ukraine-watch-101676265386485.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:48:42 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnailall_1676265412623_1676265430148_1676265430148.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made-in-India 'Tapas' drone stuns with a capture from 12,000 feet; PM Modi cheers]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indigenously developed Tapas-BH UAV captures Aero India 2023 rehearsal from 12,000 feet. The DRDO shared a stunning footage of Tapas UAV drone in action ahead of its debut. The 'Made In India' UAV will have its official debut during the air show in Bengaluru. Tapas is a medium altitude long endurance class unmanned aerial vehicle developed by DRDO. PM Narendra Modi retweeted the video of Tapas in action, captioning it as "very interesting." ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/madeinindia-tapas-drone-stuns-with-a-capture-from-12-000-feet-pm-modi-cheers-101676258020579.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/madeinindia-tapas-drone-stuns-with-a-capture-from-12-000-feet-pm-modi-cheers-101676258020579.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 08:46:18 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailTAPAS_1676258120152_1676258136649_1676258136649.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Putin's forces unleash major missile barrage as combat intensifies | Bloody battle for Donbas]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russian forces continued to shell Ukrainian cities over the weekend amid a grinding push to seize land in the east. According to Ukrainian officials, forces carried out 12 missile and 32 air strikes in Ukraine over the past 24 hours. The attacks come as Russian troops make a push for eastern industrial heartland of Donbas, which comprises of Donetsk and Luhansk. Watch this video for more battleground updates. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putins-forces-unleash-major-missile-barrage-as-combat-intensifies-bloody-battle-for-donbas-101676252803265.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/putins-forces-unleash-major-missile-barrage-as-combat-intensifies-bloody-battle-for-donbas-101676252803265.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 07:18:53 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILWAR_1676252890816_1676252912368_1676252912368.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[China to shoot down UFO spotted amid tensions with U.S. over spy balloon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chinese authorities have spotted an unidentified flying object over the Yellow Sea near the Qingdao port in Eastern China's Shandong province. As per Global Times, authorities are preparing to shoot down the UFO. This comes amid simmering tensions between China and the U.S. over 'spy' balloon. It also comes hours after a U.S. F-22 Raptor fighter jet shot down a third object in North American airspace over Canada. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-to-shoot-down-ufo-spotted-in-yellow-sea-amid-tensions-with-u-s-over-spy-balloon-report-101676221383155.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-to-shoot-down-ufo-spotted-in-yellow-sea-amid-tensions-with-u-s-over-spy-balloon-report-101676221383155.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:34:41 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676221380171_1676221380171_1676221422958_1676221422958.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[J&K leader warns amid anger over bulldozers; ‘Won’t allow non-locals to settle’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jammu and Kashmir Apni Party president Altaf Bukhari has said that his party will not allow non-locals to settle in the union territory as he criticised the administration for its ongoing anti-encroachment drive to retrieve state land. The former minister appealed to people to maintain peace and promised to reverse all “anti-people” decisions of the administration once his party comes to power. Watch this video for more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jk-leader-warns-amid-anger-over-bulldozers-won-t-allow-non-locals-to-settle-watch-101676215190202.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jk-leader-warns-amid-anger-over-bulldozers-won-t-allow-non-locals-to-settle-watch-101676215190202.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 20:52:00 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676215184254_1676215184254_1676215268622_1676215268622.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Imran Khan calls Pak Army ‘negligent’ for spike in TTP terror attacks across country]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ex-Pak pm Imran khan has blamed his own country’s security forces for rising terrorism. Imran, who is branded as 'Taliban Khan' by his critics, blamed Pak’s security forces for not doing anything when outlawed Tehreek-e-Taliban Pakistan was regrouping. Khan made these remarks during an interview with Voice of America. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/imran-khan-calls-pak-army-negligent-for-spike-in-ttp-terror-attacks-across-country-101676210647750.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/imran-khan-calls-pak-army-negligent-for-spike-in-ttp-terror-attacks-across-country-101676210647750.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:35:23 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676210643710_1676210643710_1676210669312_1676210669312.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pak betrays Putin, sends rockets to Ukraine while seeking Russian oil | Report]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pakistan has reportedly sent 10,000 rockets to Ukraine to be used in Grad rocket launchers in war against Russia. A report in the Economic Times noted that the shipment left Karachi Port last month and will arrive in Germany via Poland. The weapons will be then transferred to Ukraine. This comes at a time when the cash-strapped nation is looking to secure a deal with Russia for oil supplies. On the other hand, Russia is keeping a close watch on Pakistan's weapons movement. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/pak-betrays-russia-amid-war-sends-10-000-rockets-to-ukraine-via-nato-nation-s-port-report-101676209719088.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/pak-betrays-russia-amid-war-sends-10-000-rockets-to-ukraine-via-nato-nation-s-port-report-101676209719088.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:21:23 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/THUMB_PAK_RUSSIA_1676209857158_1676209861931_1676209861931.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[China learns 'nuclear lessons' from Putin’s war; Xi spooks with expansion aim]]></title><description><![CDATA[China is aiming to increase the number of its nuclear warheads to 900 by 2035 as a deterrent against the U.S, Chinese sources have told Kyodo news agency. President Xi Jinping has already approved the plan to double the country's nuclear arsenal. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-learns-nuclear-lessons-from-putin-s-war-xi-to-spook-biden-with-nuke-expansion-report-101676206843080.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-learns-nuclear-lessons-from-putin-s-war-xi-to-spook-biden-with-nuke-expansion-report-101676206843080.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:32:13 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676206841151_1676206841151_1676206885709_1676206885709.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Thank You Indian Brothers': Quake-hit Turks grateful for ‘Op Dost’, praise Army]]></title><description><![CDATA[India has ramped up rescue, relief and aid for earthquake-battered Turkey and Syria. India has sent its 7th IAF aircraft with 35 tonnes of humanitarian aid to both the nations. Indian Army has also set up a field hospital in Turkey's Hatay for immediate treatment of the survivors. Overwhelmed by India's support, Turkish nationals are pouring love on the Army, NDRF and other officials. A Turkish national said that Indians are more that friends, they are brothers. Watch this video to find out how India is helping Turkey and Syria.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/thank-you-indian-brothers-quake-hit-turks-grateful-for-op-dost-praise-army-watch-101676205561919.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/world-news/thank-you-indian-brothers-quake-hit-turks-grateful-for-op-dost-praise-army-watch-101676205561919.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:11:26 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/THUMBNAILThank_You_1676205653565_1676205658045_1676205658045.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jaya Bachchan angrily points finger at RS chairman Dhankar | ‘Crossed Maryada']]></title><description><![CDATA[A video of Rajya Sabha MP Jaya Bachchan angrily pointing her finger at chairman Jagdeep Dhankhar has gone viral. BJP leader Ajay Sehrawat shared a clip of the Rajya Sabha proceedings from February 9. Netizens compared her outburst with her general reaction to photojournalists. "Jaya Bachchan crossed all Maryada ki Rekha in Parliament," one user wrote. Watch this video to know more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jaya-bachchan-fumes-at-rajya-sabha-chair-points-finger-at-dhankar-angrily-crossed-maryada-101676203082348.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jaya-bachchan-fumes-at-rajya-sabha-chair-points-finger-at-dhankar-angrily-crossed-maryada-101676203082348.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:37:22 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/THUMBNAILCM_YOGI_1676203604284_1676203610338_1676203610338.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian Embassy in Kabul to be attacked? UN warns of ISIL-K threat under Taliban regime | Report]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to the United Nations the ISIL-K have threatened to launch terrorist attacks against the embassies of India, Iran and China in Afghanistan. By targeting these diplomatic missions in Afghanistan, the terror group seeks to undermine the relationship between the Taliban and the UN member states in the Central and South Asia region. These revelations were made in a report by UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres on the threat posed by ISIL. Watch this report to find out more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/indian-embassy-in-kabul-to-be-attacked-un-warns-of-isil-k-threat-under-taliban-regime-report-101676202767694.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/indian-embassy-in-kabul-to-be-attacked-un-warns-of-isil-k-threat-under-taliban-regime-report-101676202767694.html]]></guid><category>videos</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:24:39 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailKabul_1676202778097_1676202786767_1676202786767.jpg" width="1600"/></item></channel></rss>