<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/feeds/rss/videos/news/rssfeed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><title>News Videos Online: HD Videos Online, Video News Clips, Funny HD Videos Online  | Hindustan Times</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news</link><description><![CDATA[News Videos Online – Browse and Watch High Definition News Videos, Funny Videos, Technology Videos, Reviews, Bollywood Interviews, Celebrities Gossip, Controversy, Live Rally Videos and many more at hindustantimes.com.]]></description><category>videos/news</category><ttl>60</ttl><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:58:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><copyright>Copyright (C) 2019 HT Media Limited. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><language>en-US</language><docs>https://www.hindustantimes.com</docs><image><title>News Videos Online: HD Videos Online, Video News Clips, Funny HD Videos Online  | Hindustan Times</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news</link><url>https://www.hindustantimes.com/images/app-images/ht2020/desktop.png</url></image><item><title><![CDATA[India salutes Pulwama braves | '8 of 19 terrorists involved in attack killed']]></title><description><![CDATA[On the fourth anniversary of the dastardly terror attack in Pulwama that claimed the lives of over 40 soldiers, India is remembering the valour of its heroes and their supreme sacrifice. Tributes poured in from PM Narendra Modi, Home Minister Amit Shah and Congress leader Rahul Gandhi. The Army, CRPF, J&K police laid floral wreaths on the memorial for the martyrs in Pulwama. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/as-india-salutes-pulwama-bravehearts-8-of-19-terrorists-involved-in-attack-killed-i-details-101676370345789.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/as-india-salutes-pulwama-bravehearts-8-of-19-terrorists-involved-in-attack-killed-i-details-101676370345789.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:57:31 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail__1676370423786_1676370430339_1676370430339.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amit Shah rejects 'erasing Mughal history' charge amid BJP's 'Lucknow as Laxmanpur' demand]]></title><description><![CDATA[Amit Shah, the Home Minister, responds sharply to allegations of erasing Mughal history. Responding to a question on the Mughal legacy, Shah said that the BJP does not want to remove anybody's contribution to history, including that of the Mughals. The Home Minister also defended the renaming spree in BJP-ruled states and said not a single city that previously did not have an old name has been changed. The statement comes just days after U.P. Deputy CM Brajesh Pathak appealed to change the name of Lucknow as it is "well known as the city of Laxman." After this, BJP MP Sangam Lal Gupta urged Union Home Minister Amit Shah to rename U.P.'s capital city of Lucknow as "Lakhanpur" or "Laxmanpur."]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/amit-shah-rejects-erasing-mughal-history-charge-amid-bjp-s-lucknow-as-laxmanpur-demand-101676370201242.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/amit-shah-rejects-erasing-mughal-history-charge-amid-bjp-s-lucknow-as-laxmanpur-demand-101676370201242.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:56:33 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/1920x1080_THUMBNAILI_1676370296255_1676370313244_1676370313244.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lanka rejects LTTE Chief alive claim; 'Prabhakaran was killed. DNA proved it']]></title><description><![CDATA[Sri Lanka has dismissed as joke the claims that LTTE Chief Prabhakaran was alive. Pazha Nedumaran, a noted nationalist leader in Tamil Nadu, said on February 13 that the leader of the LTTE 'is doing well and a conducive atmosphere prevails for him to appear now.' "It is confirmed that he was killed on 19 May 2009. The DNA has proved it," said Colonel Nalin Herath, Sri Lanka's defence ministry spokesperson. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/joke-lanka-rejects-ltte-chief-alive-claim-prabhakaran-was-killed-dna-proved-it-101676364628352.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/joke-lanka-rejects-ltte-chief-alive-claim-prabhakaran-was-killed-dna-proved-it-101676364628352.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:22:59 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumbnail_-_1676364750318_1676364756339_1676364756339.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Treasure’: Sarojini Naidu’s 1928 speech in US gives Indians goosebumps | Viral]]></title><description><![CDATA[A 95-year-old video of Sarojini Naidu has now gone viral on social media. The video from her 1928 visit to the United States is giving goosebumps to netizens on her birth anniversary. The 55-second clip was shared by former Minister of Climate and the Environment of Norway, Erik Solheim, on Twitter. In the video, Naidu delivers a motivational speech about how, as a woman, she represents India in the 'new world.' The video has garnered over 1,81,000 views since it was shared. Watch the full video here. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/treasure-sarojini-naidu-s-1928-speech-in-u-s-gives-indians-goosebumps-in-2023-viral-101676359112045.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/treasure-sarojini-naidu-s-1928-speech-in-u-s-gives-indians-goosebumps-in-2023-viral-101676359112045.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Tue, 14 Feb 2023 12:50:11 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/14/1600x900/THUMB_NAIDU_1676359181904_1676359186635_1676359186635.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Thank PM Modi for...'; Sonam Wangchuk on saving Ladakh - Interview]]></title><description><![CDATA[The story of Sonam Wangchuk's 'climate fast' at minus 40° celsius. Environmentalist & innovator Sonam Wangchuk fasts to 'save Ladakh'. In the interview to Hindustan Times, Wangchuk said that despite the fast, sixth schedule of constitution remains a sticking point. Watch this interaction to know more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/thank-pm-modi-for-sonam-wangchuk-on-saving-ladakh-interview-101676310301985.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/thank-pm-modi-for-sonam-wangchuk-on-saving-ladakh-interview-101676310301985.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:16:13 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676310298691_1676310298691_1676310322663_1676310322663.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[NATO stockpiles in dire straits as Ukraine army needs outstrips production rate]]></title><description><![CDATA[NATO has said it will increase targets for stockpiling ammunition as Kyiv is burning through shells much faster than Western countries can produce them and after a year of conflict in Ukraine has left allied stocks badly depleted. The West needed to ramp up production, with the waiting time for large-calibre ammunition increasing to 28 months from 12 months, Stoltenberg said. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/nato-stockpiles-in-dire-straits-as-ukraine-military-needs-outstrips-production-rate-i-details-101676307622393.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/nato-stockpiles-in-dire-straits-as-ukraine-military-needs-outstrips-production-rate-i-details-101676307622393.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 22:31:52 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676307618441_1676307618441_1676307644319_1676307644319.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tamil Leader’s shocking claim about LTTE Chief Prabhakaran | ‘Alive &…' I Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[A veteran former politician in Tamil Nadu Pazha Nedumaran has made a shocking claim. He says LTTE Chief Prabhakaran, who was declared dead by the Sri Lankan govt 14 years ago, is alive and healthy. Nedumaran says Prabhakaran will soon make a public appearance. Prabhakaran, the founder of Liberation of Tigers of Tamil Eelam (LTTE), led an extensive guerrilla campaign for a separate homeland for Lankan Tamils in the island nation. He was declared dead on May 18, 2009 after an operation by the Sri Lankan army at Mullivaikal. Addressing a briefing, Pazha Nedumaran, the President of the Worlds Tamil Confederation, said 'LTTE chief Prabhakaran is alive and will appear soon. We are happy to announce this to the world. He would announce his plans for Tamil Eelam'. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/tamil-leader-s-shocking-claim-about-ltte-chief-prabhakaran-alive-will-appear-in-public-101676303334334.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/tamil-leader-s-shocking-claim-about-ltte-chief-prabhakaran-alive-will-appear-in-public-101676303334334.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 21:20:46 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676303331906_1676303331906_1676303364014_1676303364014.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Can they land?': Taliban's Air Force pilots roasted on social media I Here's Why]]></title><description><![CDATA[Taliban's Air force reportedly got three new pilots. A photograph of three men holding ‘pilot licence’ with a picture of helicopter embossed on certificate has gone viral on social media. The three bare-footed men wearing traditional Afghani attire can be seen holding certificates in their hands while sitting in an office. Watch this video for more]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/can-they-land-taliban-s-air-force-pilots-roasted-on-social-media-i-here-s-why-101676301227863.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/can-they-land-taliban-s-air-force-pilots-roasted-on-social-media-i-here-s-why-101676301227863.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:44:55 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676301224969_1676301224969_1676301259890_1676301259890.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA['Can't break Russia': Putin's ally lambasts West; Rebukes partition plot]]></title><description><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin's ally and Chechen Leader, Ramzan Kadyrov, rebukes Ukraine's stunning claims of "change on the Russian border soon." The Chechen leader said that "Russia's map can be redrawn only when Moscow decides." Ramzan Kadyrov said that such attempts to break Russia have been made by the West since the 1990s, but these overconfident people will fail. The Chechen warlord's remarks came after Alexey Danielov, Secretary of Ukraine's National Security and Defence Council, made claims about Russia's partition. Alexey Danielov said that "Russia is a colonial state that will soon split up." Watch this report for full information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/cant-break-russia-putin-s-ally-lambasts-west-chechan-warlord-rebukes-partition-plot-details-101676293377954.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/cant-break-russia-putin-s-ally-lambasts-west-chechan-warlord-rebukes-partition-plot-details-101676293377954.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:34:08 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676293375372_1676293375372_1676293396109_1676293396109.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Israel jets drop missiles on Hamas rocket factory in Gaza, destroys 'underground sites' I Watch]]></title><description><![CDATA[Israel launched overnight air strikes against a Hamas complex in Gaza in response to a rocket fired from the Palestinian enclave, the military said early Monday. Following the Israeli strikes, air raid sirens sounded in communities in near the Gaza border, the military said, but there was no immediate confirmation of retaliatory Palestinian rocket fire on Monday. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/israel-jets-drop-missiles-on-hamas-rocket-factory-in-gaza-destroys-underground-sites-i-watch-101676292348154.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/israel-jets-drop-missiles-on-hamas-rocket-factory-in-gaza-destroys-underground-sites-i-watch-101676292348154.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 18:17:03 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/hqdefault_1676292344363_1676292344363_1676292371063_1676292371063.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch IAF war machine Prachand’s aerobatic display at Aero India 2023]]></title><description><![CDATA[Aero India 2023 witnessed thrilling aerobatics by made-in-India Light Combat Helicopter 'Prachand' which left the audience mesmerised. LCH 'Prachand' is the world's only attack helicopter suitable for flying at high altitudes. It has been designed and developed by Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd and was formally commissioned into the Indian Air Force in 2022. The multi-role attack helicopter can damage enemy's air defence activities and fire a variety of air-to-ground and air-to-air missiles.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-iaf-war-machine-prachand-s-captivating-aerobatic-display-at-aero-india-2023-101676284455983.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-iaf-war-machine-prachand-s-captivating-aerobatic-display-at-aero-india-2023-101676284455983.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 16:06:32 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/prachnd_1676284519623_1676284524072_1676284524072.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Julie went & barked’: How India’s dog duo saved girl from Turkey quake rubble]]></title><description><![CDATA[On February 9, two Indian dogs were instrumental in saving the life of a 6-year-old girl, who was trapped inside the rubble in earthquake-ravaged Turkey. Four days after the miracle, dog handler Constable Kundan explains how Labrador Julie found the little girl, Beren, alive first in the rubble at the Nurdagi site. He added that Romeo and Julie succeeded where machines failed and said that without their help, the little girl could not have survived. Under 'Operation Dost,' India has sent a four-member dog squad to Turkey to help NDRF's search and rescue. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/julie-went-in-and-barked-how-india-s-dog-duo-rescued-girl-from-rubble-in-quake-hit-turkey-101676280947070.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/julie-went-in-and-barked-how-india-s-dog-duo-rescued-girl-from-rubble-in-quake-hit-turkey-101676280947070.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:09:19 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/THUMB_INDIAN_DOGS_1676281125747_1676281130395_1676281130395.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Watch Tejas jets dazzle at Aero India 2023 | PM Modi lauds ‘Aatmanirbhar Bharat’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prime Minister Narendra Modi inaugurated Asia's largest aero show, Aero India 2023, in Bengaluru. The 14th edition of the aero show will display made-in-India equipment and technologies to forge partnership with foreign companies. Addressing the inauguration ceremony, PM Modi said that Aero India reflects the country's new strengths and aspirations. The five-day event, on the theme 'The runway to a billion opportunities' will showcase India's growth in aerospace and defence capabilities. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-tejas-jets-dazzle-at-aero-india-2023-pm-modi-lauds-aatmanirbhar-bharat-101676278111145.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/watch-tejas-jets-dazzle-at-aero-india-2023-pm-modi-lauds-aatmanirbhar-bharat-101676278111145.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:20:33 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/thummotejas_1676278205480_1676278208475_1676278208475.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Op Dost: Army-made fixators help Turkey quake survivors | Display At Aero India]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indian Army has become a beacon of hope for several earthquake survivors in Turkey and Syria. The Indian Army has set up a field hospital in Turkey's Hatay, where doctors have deployed light fixators that help treat fractures. These fixators weigh only five grams and cost  ₹300 each. They are developed by the Indian Army and have been used by over 200 patients till now. Colonel Vijay Adarsh, the developer of this fixator displayed his product at the Aero India 2023 event in Bengaluru today. Watch this video for more information. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/op-dost-army-made-fixators-help-turkey-syria-quake-survivors-on-display-at-aero-india-101676276873566.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/op-dost-army-made-fixators-help-turkey-syria-quake-survivors-on-display-at-aero-india-101676276873566.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:03:36 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/13/1600x900/HT_Normal_Thumb_1676277329181_1676277334711_1676277334711.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[China to shoot down UFO spotted amid tensions with U.S. over spy balloon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chinese authorities have spotted an unidentified flying object over the Yellow Sea near the Qingdao port in Eastern China's Shandong province. As per Global Times, authorities are preparing to shoot down the UFO. This comes amid simmering tensions between China and the U.S. over 'spy' balloon. It also comes hours after a U.S. F-22 Raptor fighter jet shot down a third object in North American airspace over Canada. Watch this video for more details. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-to-shoot-down-ufo-spotted-in-yellow-sea-amid-tensions-with-u-s-over-spy-balloon-report-101676221383155.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-to-shoot-down-ufo-spotted-in-yellow-sea-amid-tensions-with-u-s-over-spy-balloon-report-101676221383155.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:34:41 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676221380171_1676221380171_1676221422958_1676221422958.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[J&K leader warns amid anger over bulldozers; ‘Won’t allow non-locals to settle’]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jammu and Kashmir Apni Party president Altaf Bukhari has said that his party will not allow non-locals to settle in the union territory as he criticised the administration for its ongoing anti-encroachment drive to retrieve state land. The former minister appealed to people to maintain peace and promised to reverse all “anti-people” decisions of the administration once his party comes to power. Watch this video for more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jk-leader-warns-amid-anger-over-bulldozers-won-t-allow-non-locals-to-settle-watch-101676215190202.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jk-leader-warns-amid-anger-over-bulldozers-won-t-allow-non-locals-to-settle-watch-101676215190202.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 20:52:00 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676215184254_1676215184254_1676215268622_1676215268622.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Imran Khan calls Pak Army ‘negligent’ for spike in TTP terror attacks across country]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ex-Pak pm Imran khan has blamed his own country’s security forces for rising terrorism. Imran, who is branded as 'Taliban Khan' by his critics, blamed Pak’s security forces for not doing anything when outlawed Tehreek-e-Taliban Pakistan was regrouping. Khan made these remarks during an interview with Voice of America. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/imran-khan-calls-pak-army-negligent-for-spike-in-ttp-terror-attacks-across-country-101676210647750.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/imran-khan-calls-pak-army-negligent-for-spike-in-ttp-terror-attacks-across-country-101676210647750.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:35:23 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676210643710_1676210643710_1676210669312_1676210669312.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[China learns 'nuclear lessons' from Putin’s war; Xi spooks with expansion aim]]></title><description><![CDATA[China is aiming to increase the number of its nuclear warheads to 900 by 2035 as a deterrent against the U.S, Chinese sources have told Kyodo news agency. President Xi Jinping has already approved the plan to double the country's nuclear arsenal. Watch this video for more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-learns-nuclear-lessons-from-putin-s-war-xi-to-spook-biden-with-nuke-expansion-report-101676206843080.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/china-learns-nuclear-lessons-from-putin-s-war-xi-to-spook-biden-with-nuke-expansion-report-101676206843080.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:32:13 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/hqdefault_1676206841151_1676206841151_1676206885709_1676206885709.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jaya Bachchan angrily points finger at RS chairman Dhankar | ‘Crossed Maryada']]></title><description><![CDATA[A video of Rajya Sabha MP Jaya Bachchan angrily pointing her finger at chairman Jagdeep Dhankhar has gone viral. BJP leader Ajay Sehrawat shared a clip of the Rajya Sabha proceedings from February 9. Netizens compared her outburst with her general reaction to photojournalists. "Jaya Bachchan crossed all Maryada ki Rekha in Parliament," one user wrote. Watch this video to know more.]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jaya-bachchan-fumes-at-rajya-sabha-chair-points-finger-at-dhankar-angrily-crossed-maryada-101676203082348.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/jaya-bachchan-fumes-at-rajya-sabha-chair-points-finger-at-dhankar-angrily-crossed-maryada-101676203082348.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:37:22 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/THUMBNAILCM_YOGI_1676203604284_1676203610338_1676203610338.jpg" width="1600"/></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian Embassy in Kabul to be attacked? UN warns of ISIL-K threat under Taliban regime | Report]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to the United Nations the ISIL-K have threatened to launch terrorist attacks against the embassies of India, Iran and China in Afghanistan. By targeting these diplomatic missions in Afghanistan, the terror group seeks to undermine the relationship between the Taliban and the UN member states in the Central and South Asia region. These revelations were made in a report by UN Secretary-General Antonio Guterres on the threat posed by ISIL. Watch this report to find out more. ]]></description><link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/indian-embassy-in-kabul-to-be-attacked-un-warns-of-isil-k-threat-under-taliban-regime-report-101676202767694.html]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/videos/news/indian-embassy-in-kabul-to-be-attacked-un-warns-of-isil-k-threat-under-taliban-regime-report-101676202767694.html]]></guid><category>videos/news</category><pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:24:39 +0530]]></pubDate><media:content height="900" medium="image" url="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2023/02/12/1600x900/HT_Normal_ThumbnailKabul_1676202778097_1676202786767_1676202786767.jpg" width="1600"/></item></channel></rss>